[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":248941,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":489588,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6 </sub>,  you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":15219,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":504808,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1476,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":506284,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"2","response_history":[" 2"],"rt":4120,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":510405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":3399,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":513805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":8616,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":522422,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":992,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":523415,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3977,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":527393,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":804,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":528197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your re sult. If  the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6231,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":534428,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":765,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":535194,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3394,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":538588,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":811,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":539401,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4443,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":543845,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1105,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":544950,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><b r /> (Re member, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2917,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":547868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":958,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":548827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4683,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":553511,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":843,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":554354,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4958,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":559312,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":922,"trial_type":"feedb ack","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":560234,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":25252,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":585488,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub >6</sub> ). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":83716,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":669205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":18312,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":687517,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":28962,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":716479,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember,  the inv erse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4011,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":720491,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1370,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":721861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2163,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":724025,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":832,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":724857,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3241,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":728098,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":10888,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":738987,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<su b>6</sub >? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6382,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":745369,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1419,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":746789,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes ","response_history":["yes"],"rt":15396,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":762186,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":81820,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":844007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub>  1. Beca use of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":75489,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":919496,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":9934,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":929430,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2427,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":931858,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":8569,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":940427,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":6008,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":946436,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":8261,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":954697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1059,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":955757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3139,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":958896,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1154,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":960050,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes they make even numbers","response_history":["yes they make een numbers","yes they mak e enumbe rs","yes they make evnumbers","yes they make evenumbers","yes they make evennumbers","yes they make even numbers"],"rt":55051,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1015102,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":52984,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1068087,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4284,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1072372,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":828,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1073201,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":6479,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1079681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3528,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1083210,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6693,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1089904,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4764,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1094669,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3204,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1097873,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. Four plus one equals 5. Because 5 is less than 9, we leave it alone.","response_history":["4+1+","4+1= 5","4+1= ","4+1","4+","4","Four ","Four plus one ew","Four plus one equals 5. Because 5 is less than (","Four plus one equals 5. Because 5 is less than 9, we leave it alone.","5Four plus one equals 5. Because 5 is less than 9, we leave it alone.","5.Four plus one equals 5. Because 5 is less than 9, we leave it alone.","5. Four plus one equals 5. Because 5 is less than 9, we leave it alone."],"rt":55111,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1152985,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. Eight plus 4 equals 12. Because 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from it, which is 3.","response_history":["3. Be","3. B","3. Eight plus 4 equals 12. Because 12 id ","3. Eight plus 4 equals 12. Because 12 id","3. Eight plus 4 equals 12. Because 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from it.","3. Eig ht plus  4 equals 12. Because 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from it, which e","3. Eight plus 4 equals 12. Because 12 is greater than 9, we subtract 9 from it, which is 3."],"rt":42713,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1195698,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"Zero, because anything added to it equals the number itself.","response_history":["Zero, becuase a","Zero, becuase ","Zero, becuase","Zero, becuas","Zero, becua","Zero, becu","Zero, because anything al","Zero, because anything added to it is","Zero, because anything added to it i","Zero, because anything added to it equals the number itself."],"rt":44301,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1239999,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inv erse of  5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4.","4"],"rt":50808,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1290807,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2978,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1293786,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Six. Because the number 3 added to it's inverse = 9.","response_history":["Sic","Sic","Sis","Six. Because the number 3 added to it's inverse = 0","Six. Because the number 3 added to it's inverse = 9."],"rt":63263,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1357050,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because 2 added to itself cannot come to equal all of the other numbers.","response_history":["No, becaue ","No, becaue","No, becau","No, becase","No, becas","No, becaa","No, because 2 added to ites","No, because 2 added to ite","No, because 2 added to itsle","No, because 2 added to itsl","No, because 2 added to its","No, because 2 added to itself cannot e","No, because 2 added to itself cannot ca","No, because 2 added to itself cannot comr to","No, because 2 added to itself cannot comr t","No, because 2 added to itself cannot comr ","No, because 2 added to itself cannot comr","No, because 2 added to itself cannot come to ewu","No, because 2 added to itself cannot come to ew","No, because 2 added to itself ca nnot com e to equal all of the other numbers."],"rt":269893,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1626944,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because 3 added to itself will come yield all of the other numbers.","response_history":["No ","No, because 3 added to itseld ","No, because 3 added to itseld","No, because 3 added to itself will come yield all of the other numbers."],"rt":26295,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1653240,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because 5 added to itself will come yield all of the other numbers.","response_history":["No,  because 5 added to itself will come yield all of the other numbers."],"rt":8494,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1661734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because 6 added to itself will come yield all of the other numbers.","response_history":["No, because 6 added to itself will come yield all of the other numbers."],"rt":4957,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1666691,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for  the arbi trary value if necessary.","rt":16977,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1683669,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"5n","response_history":["5n"],"rt":42989,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1726659,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I do not know","response_history":["I do not know"],"rt":141775,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1868435,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generato r under  +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The fist number below +n is always a generator as well as 1.","response_history":["The fisr ","The fisr","The fist number blow ","The fist number blow","The fist number blo","The fist number bl","The fist number bew","The fist number below a","The fist number below +n is always a generator as well as 1."],"rt":91998,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1960434,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":14069,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1974504,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even  number,  it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":11508,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1986012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":37587,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2023600,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"False. For example 2 is not generator under +9. 2 is also not a multip le of a  divisor of 9.","response_history":["Fals. ","Fals.","False ","False. @ i","False. @ ","False. @","False. 2 is not generator under +n","False. 2 is not generator under +9","False. f2 is not generator under +9","False. fo2 is not generator under +9","False. for 2 is not generator under +9","False. for w2 is not generator under +9","False. for wx2 is not generator under +9","False. for wxa2 is not generator under +9","False. for wxam2 is not generator under +9","False. for wxampl2 is not generator under +9","False. for wxample2 is not generator under +9","False. f2 is not generator under +9","False. 2 is not generator under +9","False. F2 is not generator under +9","False. Fo2 is not generator under +9","False. For 2 is not generator under +9","False. For e2 is not generator under +9","False. For ex2 is not generator under +9","False. For exa2 is not generator under +9","False. For exam2 is not generator under +9","False. For exampl2 is not generator under +9","False. For examp le2 is n ot generator under +9","False. For example 2 is not generator under +9. @","False. For example 2 is not generator under +9. 2 is also not a multop","False. For example 2 is not generator under +9. 2 is also not a multo","False. For example 2 is not generator under +9. 2 is also not a multiple of a divisor i","False. For example 2 is not generator under +9. 2 is also not a multiple of a divisor or ","False. For example 2 is not generator under +9. 2 is also not a multiple of a divisor or","False. For example 2 is not generator under +9. 2 is also not a multiple of a divisor of 9."],"rt":203962,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2227564,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":9519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2237083,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"A generator is always a generator.","response_history":["Al","A","A generator is always a ger","A generator is always a generator."],"rt":140332,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2377416,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":[" Never"],"rt":40266,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2417682,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1936,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2419618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"40","response_history":["40"],"rt":2390,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2422008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no  degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":2168,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2424176,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Advanced algebra and trigonometry.","response_history":["Pre-Calculus ","Pre-Calculu","Pre-Calcul","Pre-Calcu","Pre-Calc","Pre-Cal","Pre-Ca","Pre-C","Pre-","Pre","Pr","P","Advanced algebra and trigonometry. ","Advanced algebra and trigonometry."],"rt":43216,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2467393,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 -  seen it  used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":7896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2475289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","1 - never heard of it"],"rt":7115,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2482405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2852,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2485258,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2284,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2487542,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2560,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2490103,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2688,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2492792,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":5864,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2498656,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes","response_history":["yes"],"rt":3479,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2502137,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"my brain hurts now. but educational hits are always interesting.","response_history":["my brain hurts now. but eductaional hits are always interesting.","my brain hurts now. but educational hits are always interesting."],"rt":23940,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2526078,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]